iwebcam.com 2019-04-09

# Live Video Webcam Chat Room Service - Privacy | iWebcam.com

Privacy and Cookie Policy

This Agreement is Version Number 3.0.0 Date:  June 20, 2018

This Privacy Policy and Cookie Policy dated June 14, 2018 replaces all previous policies of our Privacy Policy. Your privacy is very important to us. Please take the time to review these changes regarding how we collect, store, use, and share your personal information prior to your continued use of the iWebcam.com website and Service.

We respect your privacy, are committed to protecting it and want you to be informed about the ways we protect, use and share the information that we collect. If you do not wish to have your information used in line with this Policy, you must not use our products and services and not otherwise provide us with your information.

This Privacy and Cookie Policy forms an integral part of the “Terms of Service”, and the provisions thereof, including (without limitation), the provisions regarding limitation on damages, governing law and dispute resolution, apply to this Privacy Policy.

About Us

IGENETIX CORPORATION ("We" or "Us") operates the website iWebcam.com and the Service on iWebcam.com.

PRIVACY POLICY. For the purposes of facilitating compliance with the provisions of any applicable government privacy legislation you hereby consent, through the use the website and/or Service, to IGENETIX collection of and use of your personal information necessary to allow participation of activity in whole or part on the website and Service.

Who Decides "How" and "Why" Your Personal Data is Processed?

The company, which decides how and why your personal data is processed, and which is called "Data Controller" is IGENETIX CORPORATION, a Canadian incorporated company, with contact address at Suite 301, 829 Norwest Road, Kingston, ON, CAN, K7P 2N3

 IGENETIX does not, without provision in this privacy policy, share personally identifiable information about you and your aggregate usage information that we collect with any other company.

Information we may collect and process about you

\- Information that you provide to us

\- Your IP

\- Information about chat rooms you have visited

\- Information about chat credit transactions

\- Information about chat credit purchases

\- Information we collect using cookies on your device about your use of the website and Service

\- Technical information from your device relating to the service you receive.

\- Information relating to the location of your device

\- The date and time you logged into the Service

\- The hardware, software or internet browser you use

\- Identifiers associated with cookies or other technologies that may uniquely identify your device or browser

By accessing the iWebcam.com website and use of the Service, you agree that we may collect, hold, use or otherwise process your information (including personal information) for the purpose of providing you with those products and services you request or access, and developing our business.

Payment Processing

Please note that we use a credit card processing service to complete billing to your credit card using the billing information you provide. We do not share personally identifiable information with our card processor to complete billing request.

We may share information with relevant financial institutions, if we consider it strictly necessary for fraud detection and prevention purposes. When a chargeback is requested by you or by the holder of the credit card used to make the transaction, we have, in certain cases, to share some information about you and your use of the services with the processing bank.

Personal Data We Collect From Publicly Available Sources

We collect publicly available information about you only when it is necessary to prevent fraud and illegal activities on the iWebcam.com website and Service.

This data may comprise publicly available information you share on social media like Facebook, your blog and/or site, and any other public data available on the internet.

Publications, Chat and Video Communications

When you chat and or broadcast an image or webcam in the Service, other users of the Service and our organization can see your username, messages and any publication you provide.

When you initiate a private chat with another member, only our organization and the other member can access the communications and/or image/webcam broadcast you share. Please rest assured that other Guests or Members on the Service will not have access any information about you from the moment you enter into a private chat.

How Do We Protect Your Personal Data?

We implement security measures to grant maximum protection to your personal information against unauthorized access, modification, disclosure or deletion. Your data is protected by sophisticated security systems. We implement data loss prevention systems against leakage, theft and data breach in order to ensure that our site and the entire IT infrastructure related to it are updated against the latest network security vulnerabilities. We periodically test our IT systems and do sophisticated penetration tests. We incorporate advanced security technologies in order to ensure maximum safety and safekeeping of personal information.

Rectification Of Inaccurate Or Incomplete Data

You have the right to request that we correct any inaccuracies in your personal data.

Ensure A Safe And Trustworthy Environment

We want to create and ensure a safe environment where you can peacefully enjoy our services. We use your personal data to detect and prevent fraud and other illegal activities on our site.

We also use your data to detect potential breaches to the rules of our site. The rules of the site are explained in our terms and conditions.

We use your personal information for security purposes and risk assessment, such as to authenticate you on our site and verify your identity.

We process this information given our legitimate interest in ensuring compliance with the rules of our site, fraud detection and prevention, as well as, information, system, network and cyber security.

Retention

We will retain your Personal Information for as long as necessary to provide our Services, and as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our policies. Retention periods will be determined taking into account the type of information that is collected and the purpose for which it is collected, bearing in mind the requirements applicable to the situation and the need to destroy outdated, unused information at the earliest reasonable time. Under applicable regulations, we will keep records containing customer Personal Information, account signup agreements, communications and anything else as required by applicable laws and regulations.

Google Analytics

We may use Google Analytics to track performance. Google Analytics uses persistent cookies to track visitor sessions, visitors across multiple sessions, and referral sources to the iWebcam website. We also track the performance of promotional links to our site.

In compliance with the Google Analytics Terms of Service, at no time is personally identifiable information passed to Google Analytics. Note that Google Analytics stores its data within the United States and is subject to US laws. Those wishing to opt out of Google Analytics data collection should use the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/ url.

AddThis

AddThis tools provide website owners with the capability to enable users to instantly share webpages, blogs, news, photos, videos, and other content to the most popular social networks and other destinations via a browser plug-in or website plug-in.  We use services provided by AddThis to help visitors share content that they find useful on our website across multiple social networks and platforms. AddThis uses cookies to collect data on how our content is shared. You can learn how to opt-out of AddThis as well as find further information on AddThis terms and conditions of use and data privacy at:http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy

COOKIES POLICY

You should be aware that when you use the iWebcam.com website or Service we may collect information using cookies or similar technologies.

What Are Cookies And How Do They Work?

Cookies are small files that are downloaded to your computer or mobile device when you visit a website and or Service. Your browser sends these cookies back to the website and or Service every time you visit the site again, so it can recognize you. This allows websites to tailor what you see on the screen.

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually remove or reject browser cookies through the settings on your browser or device. Keep in mind, though, that blocking cookies may negatively affect your use of the services on our site.

A “flash cookie” is a data file placed on your device via the Adobe Flash plug-in, which may be built-in or downloaded by you to your computer or other device.  Flash cookies may be used for various purposes, such as enabling a Flash feature and remembering your preferences. If you choose to adjust your Flash privacy settings in your device, some features of the Service may not function properly. For more information about the privacy choices Adobe offers: http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html

Contacting Us And Accessing Your Personal Information

If you have any queries or comments about this Privacy and Cookies Policy please contact us at: support@iWebcam.com

If you wish to review or receive a copy of the personal information we hold about you please write to us at:

Attention: Data Protection Officer

IGENETIX CORPORATION

Suite 301

829 Norwest Rd.

Kingston, ON, CAN

K7P2N3

privacy@igenetix.com

Changes To This Privacy and Cookies Policy

We reserve the right to make changes to our Privacy and Cookies Policy. Changes to this policy will be posted here and will become effective as of the updated effective date. Your continued use of our website or platform will signify your acceptance of these changes.
